Guide to the Victorian Society of America, Metropolitan Chapter Records 1950s-2019 (bulk 1970-2015) MS 3205
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Paper-based Files, 1950s-2019 (bulk 1970-2015); 12 Linear feet in 12 record cartons
  - History—Compiled List of Annual Meeting Venues (Incomplete), 1982-2001 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
    Consists of rough handwritten notes on legal pad paper, not all venues and dates have been recorded.
  - History—Compiled List of VSNY Lectures + Tours, 1967-2006 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
  - History—Compiled List of VSNY Awards, 1976-2005 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
  - History—Dorothy Miner (1938-2008), NYC LPC Attorney, circa 2008 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10A)
    Dorothy Miner (1938-2008) was chief counsel with the NYC Landmarks Preservation Commission (LPC) and her work there helped to create a legal process for landmark designations in the city. Among other items, contains obituaries, histories, and correspondence about her life and work.
  - VSNY Archives Committee, 2004, 2005, 2017 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10B)
    Among other items, contains correspondence, planning, progress reports, budgets and retention schedules for the VSNY archives project. Bulk is from 2017.
  - VSA Files, 1950s (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
    Holds only Folder Code T, which is personal ephemera collected by Margot Gayle, 1950s.
  - VSA Files, 1960s (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
    Holds only Folder Code T, which is personal ephemera collected by Margot Gayle, 1960s.
  - VSNY Files, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 13-28)
  - VSNY Files, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 29-43)
    The set holds Folder Codes: B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, O, P, Q, T, U, X
    Folder Notes:
    K—Among other items, includes deliberations about Chapters, dues, national representation, etc.
    O—Note that at this time, all memberships were handled by VSA national with administrative discussions (K) between Chapters and VSA on best approaches for funding Chapter operations and developing Chapter bylaws.
    P—See K for additional information on Chapter operations.
    U—Letterhead for 1974 Board only.
    X—Among other items, includes first printing of "Cast Iron Architecture in New York City" (©1974, Friends of Cast Iron Architecture) and two black and white 35mm contact sheets.
    G/T/X—Note that correspondence, activities, and materials may overlap between these folders.
    Among other items, includes first printing of "Cast Iron Architecture in New York City" (©1974, Friends of Cast Iron Architecture); two black and white 35mm contact sheets; and deliberations about Chapters, dues, national representation, etc.
  - VSNY Files, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1-17)
    The set holds Folder Codes: B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, N, O, P, Q, R, T, U, X
    Folder Notes
    N—Among other items, includes thermal copy of first VSA Award document.
    P—First by-laws for Chapters.
  - VSNY Files, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 18-31)
    The set holds Folder Codes: B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, Q, R, T
    T—Among other items, includes black and white negatives and contact sheets.
  - VSNY Files, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 32-47)
    The set holds Folder Codes: B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P, Q, R, S, T, X
    H—Among other items, includes color photograph prints and negatives.
  - VSNY Files, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 48-64)
    In 1983, VSNY was the host of the VSA National Annual Meeting. Among other items, includes planning for various events for conference attendees.
  - VSNY Files, 1985 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1-15)
    The set holds Folder Codes: A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P, Q, R, T
    H—Among other items, includes party photographs by Bob Kaufman noted as "mid-1980s."
  - VSNY Files, 1986 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 16-31)
    Among other items, includes files from the VSNY "The Heroic Age of Sculpture Symposium" and Sherman Monument preservation project.
  - VSNY Files, 1987 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 32-49)
    Among other items, includes Sherman Monument preservation project.
  - VSNY Files, 1988 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 50-65)
  - VSNY Files, 1989 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1-16)
    Among other items, includes black and white print of photograph of Margot Gayle and others and signed by Mayor Koch.
  - VSNY Files, 1990 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 17-32)
  - VSNY Files, 1991 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 33-48)
  - VSNY Files (9 of 16 folders), 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 49-57)
    Among other items, includes color print, black and white prints, 35mm black and white negatives and contact sheets.
  - VSNY Files (7 of 16 folders), 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1-7)
  - VSNY Files, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8-22)
  - VSNY Files, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 23-36)
  - VSNY Files, 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 37-50)
    Among other items, includes color photo of Margot Gayle (1908-2008) with Phillip Johnson (1906-2005) and ephemera from the 1998 "Margot Gayle Birthday Bash."
  - VSNY Files (10 of 20 folders), 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 51-59)
  - VSNY Files (10 of 20 folders), 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1-10)
    Among other items, includes 35mm color slides of award recipient, Hudson Museum.
  - VSNY Files, 2002 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11-27)
    Holds a floppy disk labeled as "partially defective." To the extent possible the files have been preserved; see Series II item 2001-2002_VSNY_Membership_JEggebeen.
  - VSNY Files, 2003 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 28-42)
    Among other items, includes 35mm presentation slides of some Award nominee projects and publications. The Margot Gayle Fund was founded in 2003 and approved by Membership at the Annual Meeting.
  - VSNY Files, 2004 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1-18)
    Among other items, includes 35mm presentation slides; black and white photo prints of buildings considered for landmarking; color photo print of VSA Summer School attendees; and first Margot Gayle Fund grant application.
  - VSNY Files, 2005 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 19-36)
    Among other items, holds a CD with a PowerPoint presentation. The file has been preserved; see Series II item 2005_VSNY_AnnualMtg_PresDeck. Also includes color photograph prints of Margot Gayle at 97th birthday party and NYC Proclamation; and materials for campaign to expand the SoHo-Cast Iron Historic District.
  - VSNY Files, 2006 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1-18)
    Among other items, includes guidelines for Margot Gayle Fund; materials for campaign to expand the SoHo-Cast Iron Historic District, proposal, walking tour, images, and PowerPoint presentation; Survey of Cast-Iron Fronts in New York City, the first Margo Gayle Fund commissioned report; contacts and letters of support; "I am A Friend of Cast Iron" fold-over metal badges; and miscellaneous research materials.
  - VSNY Files, 2007 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 19-34)
    Among other items, includes campaign to expand the SoHo-Cast Iron Historic District.
  - VSNY Files, 2008 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1-19)
    Margot Gayle died in September 2008. Among other items, includes newspaper clippings about her 100th birthday and her death. Also includes campaign to expand the SoHo-Cast Iron Historic District.
  - VSNY Files, 2009 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 20-33)
  - VSNY Files, 2010 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 34-51)
    Among other items, includes first materials for Hands On History classes; NYC Landmarks Preservation Commission, SoHo-Cast Iron Historic Designation District Extension, Designation Report; and VSNY "I am A Friend of Cast Iron" fold-over metal badges.
  - VSNY Files, 2011 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1-19)
    Among other things, holds a CD with photos of the annual meeting. The files have been preserved; see Series II item 2011_VSNY_AnnualMtg_Pics_PMargolis. Also holds a CD with a PowerPoint presentation. The file has been preserved; see Series II item 2011_TAFennimanArch_VSNY_AwardEntry. And includes copies of the third printing of "Cast Iron Architecture in New York City", produced by Friends of Cast Iron Architecture (FCIA; ©1974, 1983); and VSNY new logo sketches.
  - VSNY Files, 2012 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 20-34)
  - VSNY Files, 2013 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 35-50)
  - VSNY Files, 2014 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 51-66)
  - VSNY Files, 2015 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1-13)
    Among other items, includes testimony regarding sites in the NYC Landmark Preservation Commission (LPC) backlogged applications.
  - VSNY Files, 2016 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 14-27)
  - VSNY Files, 2017 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 28-43)
  - VSNY Files, 2018 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 44-48)
  - VSNY Files, 2019 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 49)
    Holds only Folder Code H (special events).
  - VSNY Newsletters (Redundant Copies), 1991-2014 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 50-58)
    Individual year folders contain up to three copies of each extant VSNY newsletter. (Not all years and issues exist.) This folder contains extra copies with some copies damaged or soiled.
  - VSNY Annual Meeting Invitations (Redundant Copies), 2004-2018 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 59)
    Individual year folders contain up to three copies of each extant VSNY Annual Meeting Invitation. (Not all years exist.) This folder contains extra copies with some copies damaged or soiled.
- Series II. Digital Materials, circa 1966-circa 2014; 7.69 Gigabytes (7,887 digital files)
  This series consists of digital files transferred from several CDs and one 3.5-inch floppy disk in the collection. These digital records consist primarily of routine business matters such as meeting minutes, financial reports, membership management, preservation advocacy efforts, newsletters, and annual meeting presentations. Scans of some early (1960s-70s) historical documents related to the organization are here, accounting for the pre-digital year in the series' date range. Also included here are the files from a set of 3 CDs of a 2010 oral history interview of William (Bill) J. Dane.
  The container list documents each of the individual CDs/floppy from which files were preserved, with a summary of their content. The title used in the container list for the media was established by the processing archivist because of the ambiguity of the original media's inscription, which is also recorded in the container list's description. A full manifest of the individual files comprising the series is available from the reference librarian upon request.
  Digital files were not retrieved from damaged, duplicate, and commercially available CDs or due to disk formatting issues, though the physical media itself remains in the collection. Some of the preserved files may not be accessible due to file and/or media corruption and/or because the library does not have the proprietary software necessary to make the information they contain accessible.
  The series opens with an entry for the physical media from which most of the digital files were preserved. (Some of the CDs were found in the paper-based files and, after the files were preserved, were left there; those are noted in the container list.) The remainder of the series lists the digital files, with each entry representing the files preserved from one CD/floppy. This is in roughly chronological order of the digital file date range.
  - Digital Media (RESTRICTED), circa 2000-circa 2013 (Offsite-box 12)
    The external media carriers (CDs and floppy disk) were retained for context and may be requested, but patrons may only use the preserved digital files listed below.
  - 1966-2014_VSNY_History-Awards-Misc, circa 1966-circa 2014 (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 1)
    Files from CD, 6.5 MB, 45 files. Original media inscription: "VSNY."
    Scans of VSA (1966) and VSA Metropolitan Chapter founding documents (1970) as well as tax exemption certificates. Correspondence relating to VSNY Awards (2007-2013), including new letterhead, and miscellaneous memos, scripts, and Margot Gayle Fund administration memos.
  - 2000-2003_VSNY_Newsletter_MiscFiles (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 2)
    Files from CD, marked "Partially Defective," 421.4 MB, 983 files. Original media inscription: "VIC SOC #1"]
    Newsletter and miscellaneous files (Bylaws.doc), bulk organized into folders:
    – 2000
    – 2001 (Fall - General, Fall - Newsletter, Spring - Awards, Spring - General)
    – 2002 (Fall - General, Fall - Newsletter, Spring - Awards, Spring - General, Spring - Newsletter)
    – 2003 Fall - General
    – 2003 Fall - Newsletter
    – 2003 Spring - General
    – 2003 Spring - Newsletter
    – Misc Files & Duplicates
    – Vic Soc Extra Files—Note that some materials may be earlier drafts of published newsletter content.
  - 2004_VSNY_AnnualMtg_PresDeck (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 3)
    File from CD, 21.3 MB, 1 file. Original media inscription: "VIC SOC ANNUAL MTG 04 FINAL". PowerPoint (PPT) presentation deck for the 2004 VSNY 37th Annual Meeting.
  - 2001-2002_VSNY_Membership_JEggebeen (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 4)
    Files from 3.5-inch floppy disk, 910.1 KB, 33 files. Original floppy disk in Box 6, 2002, folder Code O) Membership. Original media inscription: "VSA Membership 2002-O"
    Contents appear to include dependent database files, software unknown, and some files read a 0 KB and may not be useable. Created and/or administered by Janna Eggebeen. Some Word (DOC) files include Membership flyer and member correspondence.
  - 2004_VSNY_SoHoCastIronPics_Crosby (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 5)
    Files from CD, 39.1 MB, 48 files. Original media inscription: "VSA SoHo Crosby 3.05"
    Photos of buildings along Crosby Street, SoHo, Manhattan, taken in December 2004. Photos used for SoHo Cast Iron research, survey, and application to expand the NYC LPC SoHo-Cast Iron Historic District (approved 2010). Photographer(s) unknown.
  - 2004_VSNY_SoHoCastIronPics_Bway (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 6)
    Files from CD, 120.8 MB, 136 files. Original media inscription: "VSA SoHo W. Bwy 3.05 (1 of 2 CDs)"
    Photos of buildings along West Broadway, SoHo, Manhattan, taken in December 2004 (bulk) and March 2005. Photos used for SoHo Cast Iron research, survey, and application to expand the NYC LPC SoHo-Cast Iron Historic District (approved 2010). Photographer(s) unknown.
  - 2004-2006_VSNY_MiscFiles (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 7)
    Files from CD, 639.4 MB, 1,146 files of various formats, including DOC, XLS, PDF, JPG, TIF, and others. Original media inscription: "VIC SOC 2004-6"
    Miscellaneous files organized into folders titled:
    – 2004 (sub-folders for lectures, tours, and newsletter)
    – 2005 (sub-folders for lectures, tours, and newsletter)
    – 2006 (sub-folders for lectures, tours, and newsletter)
    – Administrative (Among other items, contains Chapter Annual Reports files with VSA)
    – Agendas and Minutes
    – Annual Meeting
    – Board Member Directories
    – By-laws
    – Financial Reports, Logos, Letterheads, Etc
    – Membership
    – Preservation.
  - 2004-2010_VSNY_Admin-MG-Event-SoHo (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 8)
    Files from CD, 489.7 MB, 528 files of various formats, including DOC, PUB, XLS, PPT, PDF, JPG, GIF, PSD, TIF, and others. Original media inscription: "Joyce Pres. Comm + Misc Files Melissa"
    Miscellaneous VSNY files organized into folders: Margot Gayle event; Minutes; Preservation Committee; SoHo Project; as well as other unorganized files in the top-level folder. Contains materials for LPG SoHo-Cast Iron Historic District Expansion application. Authors/administrators include 2010 VSNY President Joyce Mendelsohn and Publicity Committee member Melissa Baldock.
  - 2004-2010_VSNY_LecturePR_MBaldock (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 9)
    Files from CD, 69.3 MB, 157 files of various formats including DOC, JPG, PDF, and others. Original media inscription: "Lecture Comm Melissa 2009-2010"
    VSNY 2004-2010 lecture communications and press releases, created and/or administered by Melissa Baldock, VSNY. Contents organized into Folders: Fall 2009, Fall 2010 lectures, Lecture Committee Administration, New Folder, Spring 2009, and Spring 2010. Contents may be further organized by presenter name.
  - 2005_VSNY_AnnualMtg_PresDeck (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 10)
    File from CD, 29.8 MB, 1 file. Original media is located in Box 7, Folder 21, 2005, Folder Code C) Annual Meeting. Original media inscription: "ANNUAL MEETING 2005 FINAL." PowerPoint (PPT) presentation deck for the 2005 VSNY 38th Annual Meeting (2005-05-24).
  - 2005-2009_VSNY_MiscFiles_TZukowski (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 11)
    Files from CD. Original media inscription: "T. Zukowski Victorian Society Files 2005-2009"
    It is assumed that Karen Zukowski is the primary author/administrator of these files. The earliest files date from 2002. Various miscellaneous files arranged in folders:
    – Boss Tweed lecture info,
    - By laws,
    – Cast Iron contractor,
    – d'ambrosio stuff,
    – images for Spring 05 Vic Soc lectures,
    – johnonsteps[1],
    – KSherry_summary,
    – LECTURE COMM ORGANIZATIONAL,
    – LettertoJeffSholeenrebylaws,
    – materials for Spring 2007 pr,
    – MINUTES, robertson bios,
    – Rosenberg 19c article,
    – schecter_author,
    – spring 08 lectures,
    – Stirton photos,
    – Vic Soc fall 2005 images,
    – Vic Soc Fall 2006 lecture information,
    – Vic Soc Fall 2008 lectures,
    – Vic Soc lecs Fall 2007,
    – Vic Soc nominating committee#0DAD,
    – Vic Soc Spring 06 lecturer resumes,
    – Vic Soc Spring 08 lectures,
    – Vic Soc Spring 2006 images,
    – Vic Soc spring 2009 lectures,
    – Zabar lecture,
    – as well as other unorganized files in the top-level folder.
  - 2006_VSNY_AnnualMtg_Pres-AwardCert (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 12)
    Files from CD, 36.6 MB, 23 files. Original media inscription: "VIC SOC ANNUAL MTG 2006"
    PowerPoint (PPT) presentation file with 75 slides, and VSNY 2006 Award Certificates (DOC) for the 2006 VSNY Annual Meeting. Note that this file is a version of the 86-slide PPT file in "2006_VSNY_AnnualMtg_PresDeck," and is a different size and modification date. The original media for "2006_VSNY_AnnualMtg_PresDeck" was labeled "Final."
  - 2006_VSNY_AnnualMtg_PresFinal (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 13)
    File from CD, 34.3 MB, 1 file. Original media inscription: "VIC SOC 2006 ANNUAL MTG -FINAL-." PowerPoint (PPT) presentation file with 86 slides for the 2006 VSNY Annual Meeting. Note that a 75-slide version of this presentation deck with the same name exists in folder "2006_VSNY_AnnualMtg_Pres-AwardCert." The original media for this file was labeled "Final."
  - 2008_MGayle_100thBirthday_Pics (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 14)
    Files from CD, 7.3 MB, 104 files. Original media inscription: "Margot Gayle 100th B-Day 2008." Digital images (JPG) taken at the 100th birthday party for Margot Gayle (1908-2008) on May 14, 2008. Most photos are named, in some part, for those depicted in them. Photographer(s) is unknown.
  - 2008_VSNY_GCT_Pic_JonathanWallen (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 15)
    File from CD, 367.7 KB, 1 file. Original media inscription: "VIC SOC Fall 2008 Lecture; Warren + Wetmore GCT; Tennoyer + Walker; Lamps(?) Grand Central Terminal; Photo by Jonathan Wallen"
    Contains one digital image (JPG) showing a ramp and lighting fixture within Grand Central Terminal (GCT). Digital image by Jonathan Wallen. Image may have been used in the Fall 2008 Lecture about Warren + Wetmore, architects of Grand Central Terminal (1913).
  - 2009_VSNY_AnnualMtg_PresDeck (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 16)
    File from CD, 24.0 MB, 1 file. Original media inscription: "19 May 2009; Victorian Society Metro Chapter Presentation @6:30 pm. Problems? Call: 212-849-8376 Jackie K." PowerPoint (PPT) presentation deck for the 2009 VSNY Annual Meeting (2006-05-03).
  - 2009_VSNY_NominatingCom_KZukowski (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 17)
    Files from CD, 2.8 MB, 60 files of various formats, including DOC, DOCX, XLS, PAGES, and PDF. Original media inscription: "Metro Chapter—Victorian Society Nominating Committee files from Karen Zukowski, May 20 2009."
    Administrative records and correspondence regarding candidates for VSNY Board. Contents arranged in Folders: 2008 Nom Comm, 2009 Nom Comm, and orientation docs, Nom Comm.
  - 2010_VSNY_AnnualMtg_Pics_PMargolis (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 18)
    Files from CD, 79.5 MB, 50 files. Original media inscription: "Victorian Soc. Annual Meeting Eldridge St. Shul; Paul Margolis PaulM@att.net 5/11/10"
    Photos taken at the VSNY 2010 Annual Meeting, held at the Museum at Eldridge Street Synagogue (2010-05-12), and showing various speakers and guests. All images enclosed in a folder named "Victorian Soc. Choices 5-11-10." Photography Credit: Paul Margolis.
  - 2010_VSNY_HistoryInterview_BDane-01 (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 19)
    Files from CD, 1.2 GB, 6 files. Original media inscription: "VSNY Bill Dane Oral History-Disk 1/1 2010"
    One of three related media items containing an oral history interview of William (Bill) J. Dane (1923-2019) by Jeffrey P. Sholeen (1953-2022), recorded on December 4, 2010, in Chelsea, Manhattan. Contains final agreement forms, AIF files of recorded interview, and final transcript (inclusive of Dane's corrections).
  - 2010_VSNY_HistoryInterview_BDane-02 (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 20)
    Files from CD, 691.6 MB, 12 files. Original media inscription: "VSNY Bill Dane Oral History-Disk 1 of 2 2010"
    Second of three related media items containing an oral history interview of William (Bill) J. Dane (1923-2019) by Jeffrey P. Sholeen (1953-2022), recorded on December 4, 2010, in Chelsea, Manhattan. Contains (assumed) working files including agreement forms, RoxioRestore.exe file, AIF and AIF.SPN processing files.
  - 2010_VSNY_HistoryInterview_BDane-03 (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 21)
    Files from CD, 504.3 MB, 10 files. Original media inscription: "VSNY Bill Dane Oral History-Disk 2 of 2 2010-Audio transcript from interview w/Jeff Sholeen on December 4, 2010 Chelsea NYC"
    Third of three related media items containing an oral history interview of William (Bill) J. Dane (1923-2019) by Jeffrey P. Sholeen (1953-2022), recorded on December 4, 2010, in Chelsea, Manhattan. Contains (assumed) working files including RoxioRestore.exe file, AIF and AIF.SPN processing files and copy of final transcript DOC file.
  - 2011_TAFennimanArch_VSNY_AwardEntry (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 22)
    Files from two CDs, 161.3 MB, 60 files. The original CDs are filed in Box 10, Folder 11, 2011, Folder Code N) Awards and Scholarships. No original media inscription.
    Thomas A. Fenniman Architect VSNY Award entry materials showing before, during, and after restoration of St. Francis Xavier Church. Digital images (JPGs) supplied by Thomas A. Fenniman Architect.
  - 2011_VSNY_MGayleHistory_GVSHP (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 23)
    Files from CD, 4.7MB, 23 files. Original media inscription: "Margot Gayle GVSHP Panel 3/2/11"
    Historic images, various dates, of Margot Gayle (1908-2008) used at a panel discussion hosted by the Greenwich Village Society for Historic Preservation (2011-03-02). Photographer(s) unknown.
  - 2011_VSNY_AnnualMtg_Pics_PMargolis (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 24)
    Files from CD, 384.3 MB, 209 images. Original CD filed in Box 10, Folder 3, 2011, Folder Code C) Annual Meeting. Original media inscription: "Victorian Society Annual Meeting 5/17/11; Photos: Paul Margolis"
    Digital images (JPG) taken at the 2011 VSNY Annual Meeting (2010-05-17) of speakers, awards, and attendees. Folders include all photos and a subfolder, "Vict. Soc. Choices 5-17-11." Photography Credit: Paul Margolis.
  - Duplicate Files Media (Digital-folder MS3205, Digital-file 25)
    Contains contents of CDs which contained duplicate copies of files, digital images, etc.